seemomsuck.com 2019-05-11

# 3rd Shift Video - Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy statement sets forth the policies and practices with respect to information or data that is received or gathered regarding Members, visitors and Users of TeenTugs.com, EbonyTugs.com, Mylked.com, Petite18.com, TeasePOV.com, Over40Handjobs.com, SeeMomSuck.com, TeenTugs.com, Familylust.com, TugPass.com, FinishHim.com and 3rd Shift Video (collectivly "Sites", "Us", "We", "Our") or the services provided by this Site. 

We are committed to protecting your privacy and security. The following information is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing and using this Site. By accessing and using this Site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use this Site. As provided below, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. Such changes will be effective immediately upon posting. We request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully and consult it regularly. 

**I. Information Collection and Use**

A. Information Collection. We are the owner of the information collected on this Site. When users utilize our services, we collect information such as name, address, email address, IP address and username. We may collect information from our users when the user signs on to our home page, enters account information, and otherwise uses our services. Information is collected through completion of on-line forms. If a user refuses to provide the required information for a specific service, the user will not be able to utilize that service. 

B. Information Use. We use information for the following purposes: to fulfill your requests for products and services, to contact you and to send out special promotional offers. We also use your information for market research data purposes to increase the user's experience. We reserve the right to formulate statistical models to accomplish this Site's goals thru surveys, contests and promotional events. 

**II. Registration and Order Forms**  
To use services on this Site, a user must complete an on-line form. The form requires a user to provide us with certain contact information. This information is used for contacting you regarding a problem with your account and/or our services at this Site, and managing the user's account. From time to time, we may also ask that you provide us with additional information so that we can better tailor our services to meet your needs. 

**III. Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive when the user visits certain wesites and contains information about the user. We will not use cookies to collect personal identification information from our users. However, we will use cookies internally for purposes of providing additional personalized services to our users. For example, we may use cookies to determine whether the user completed the join form, to tell us if the user's browser accepts cookies, to inform us when the user has successfully logged in, to determine if the user is using the auto-login feature, to store the user's preferences, and to determine whether the user has seen a pop-up from the promotional pages. Please note that some of our business partners may also use cookies on this Site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

**IV. Sharing and Third Party Distribution of Information**  
We reserve the right to distribute, or otherwise make available, personally identifiable information about our users to third parties. We are not responsible for the third parties use of this information. We also reserve the right to make such information available to third parties in the future in order to enhance and personalize our services, or in the case of bankruptcy, sale of an asset, business or division, a merger or acquisition, or similar change of ownership. This Site may also make forums and message boards available to our users. Please remember that information disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**V. Law Enforcement**  
We will cooperate with law enforcement authorities, private-party litigants, and others seeking information about our end users to the extent required by applicable law. Examples of such cooperation include compliance with discovery requests, subpoenas and court orders. 

**VI. Links**  
This Site may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave this Site they should read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. 

**VII. Security**  
We agree to use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the information you have provided to us from unauthorized access by using encryption and other security measures. Although we take reasonable efforts to make our network secure, we cannot guarantee that the security measures in place will stop third-party "hackers" from illegally accessing your information. We encourage you to contact us if you are interested in learning more about our security measures. 

**VIII. Children**  
This Site is NOT intended for children under 18 years of age (21 years of age depending on the age of majority in your jurisdiction). This Site does not target children, nor do we solicit data, or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from them. We encourage parents and legal guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on the websites their children visit. 

**IX. Data Quality, Access, and Updating Personal Information**  
We will take reasonable steps to ensure that the information and data is complete, accurate, and timely for the user's desired purposes. If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as email address), is inaccurate, or if a user no longer desires our services, the user should contact us to correct or update the information. 

**X. Information Retention**  
We retain all user information indefinitely. 

**XI. Newsletters, Correspondence, and Opt-out Policy**   
We may send our users e-mails or other notices regarding new services, promotional events, or other information that may be of general interest. Users who no longer wish to receive materials from us may opt-out of receiving these communications by contacting us or opting-out by following the instructions located at the bottom of each e-mail message we send. We will comply will all requests for removal. 

**XII. Notification of Changes**   
A. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such changes on this Site. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective immediately upon posting such changes. If you access or use this Site, you are required to periodically check our Privacy Policy for any changes. If you continue to access or use this Site after we have changed our Privacy Policy, you manifest your assent to the changes to our Privacy Policy. 

B. If we use your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated in the Privacy Policy at the time that such information was collected, we will attempt to notify you of such changes. You agree that if we send you an e-mail to the e-mail address reflected in our records, such e-mail will constitute acceptable notice to you of the change in our policy. The notice will provide you with an opportunity to "opt-out" so that we may not use your personally identifiable information in a manner which is different from the manner described at the time that you provided us with such information. If you do not affirmatively "opt-out" pursuant to the instructions provided to you in the notice, then you agree that we may use your personally identifiable information in the manner described in the notice. (If we have no e-mail address for you, or if we do not have a current e-mail address for you, then you agree that adequate notice of the change in our policy will be effected by posting such a change onto our Privacy Policy, which shall also disclose information about how you may "opt-out" so that we may not use your personally identifiable information in a manner which is materially different from the manner described at the time that you provided us with such information. If you do not affirmatively "opt-out" pursuant to the instructions posted within the time period specified, then you agree that we may use your personally identifiable information as described in the posted notice).   

**XIII. Contact Information**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us by sending an e-mail. Please provide us with your name, e-mail address and account username if applicable so that we can provide prompt service.
